(Vet:)We're not supposed
to let people in back, but...
(Vet:)...I think I can make an exception.
(Raj:)-Thank you.
-Come on.
(Vet:)-By the way, I sang her Katy Perry.
-Oh, yeah?
(Vet:)And I don't care what that obnoxious
parrot back there says. I crushed it.
(Penny:)I think there's something going
on between the two of them.
(Leonard:)Maybe, but you also think
nine minutes isn't a while,
(Leonard:)so what do you know?
-You OK?
.Why?
(Amy:)Because my boyfriend's off
playing choo-choo with some weirdo?
(Leonard:)Well, to be fair,
they're both weirdos.
(Amy:)I don't know what made me think
tonight would be any different.
(Bernadette:)Well, just the fact that you got
him up here still says a lot.
(Bernadette:)To be honest, I bet Howie 200
bucks it wasn't gonna happen.
(Howard:)I'm going to the LEGO store
to get a big-ass R2-D2.
(Bernadette:)See? It's not just Sheldon.
They're all idiots.